A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Abe Fellowships, Record Group 3, Series 8 FA1871
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meeting files, 1989-1995; 5; 1.71 Cubic Feet 4.5 document boxes: 4.5 letter boxes
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Meeting, October 1993 - Agenda (Box 24, Folder 368)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Meeting, October 1994 - Agenda (Box 24, Folder 369-370)
  - 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference workshop readings - Regulation and technology, 1991-1994 (Box 24, Folder 371)
  - 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference workshop readings - Environment, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 372)
  - 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference workshop readings - United Nations, 1989-1994 (Box 25, Folder 373)
  - 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference workshop readings - Regional economic cooperation, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 374)
  - 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference workshop readings - China, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 375)
  - Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1994, Montauk, New York - Logistics (Box 25, Folder 376)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Mid-Term Review, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 377)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Accountability Requirements, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 378)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Cooperation (CGP) 4 concerns about Abe Fellowship Program, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 379)
  - Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1994, Montauk, New York - Correspondence regarding publication, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 380)
  - Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1994, Montauk, New York - Briefing book (Box 25, Folder 381)
  - Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1994, Montauk, New York - Background, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 382)
  - Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1994, Montauk, New York - Notes and thanks (Box 26, Folder 383)
- Budget files, 1991-1995; 6; .57 Cubic Feet 1.5 document boxes: 1.5 letter boxes
  This subseries documents the Social Science Research Council (SSRC) Abe Fellowship Program's activities for monitoring expenses in relation to its grant funding, including grants from the Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP). There are budget books for specific years of the Abe Fellowship Program's operations from between 1991 and 1994. There is also a budget book specific to the 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference.
  Material formats found within the subseries include invoices, payment requests, correspondence, and grant status summaries.
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1992-1993 Budget Book, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 384)
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1994 Abe Fellows' Conference budget book, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 385-386)
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1991-1992 Budget Book (Box 27, Folder 387)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted – confidential material
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1993-1994 Budget Book, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 388-389)